#### **About me**

I am a young Strategist intrigued by culture and its power to tell compelling stories. Driven by curiosity, diversity, and cross-pollination of ideas, I thrive on an iterative problem-solving process focusing on people and purpose. Having started my journey at the intersection of fashion and business, I developed an appreciation of macro-micro environments and their impact on human behaviour.

Moving on to gain invaluable agency experience oriented me to approach challenges by combining strategic thinking, clear communication and creativity. I bring open-mindedness, a willingness to unlearn and relearn, and a multicultural work ethic as my USP to creatively solve problems and

# **Relevant Work Experience**

#### Freelance Strategy Consultant, Milan, Italy (02,2022-08,2023)

Clients (based in India): Vat Production House, Antkind Collective.

- Analysed existing business cases and created new business pitch decks.
- Mined culture on purpose-driven young indie musicians to develop branded stories involving indie creators.

## Content Consultant with Lakmé Fashion Week (LFW), Mumbai, India (01.2021-09.2021)

Lakmé Fashion Week (LFW) is Reliance Brands' exclusive IP. Clients: Logitech, boAt, Nexa, Lakmé, TRESemmé, Marie Claire, National Diamond Council (NDC), Bata.

Reporting: Head of Fashion Business

- Led content production team, production budget and talent collaborations.
- Liaised with internal and external stakeholders to craft a successful phygital event communication.
- Concepted branded stories translating contemporary youth culture to position stakeholders amidst evolving Indian fashion and lifestyle.
- Concepted event experiences and communication focusing on sustainability and conscious purchase behaviours.

# Jr. Brand and Creative Strategist with FiloBlu, Milan, Italy (09.2019-09.2020)

Clients - Kimbo, Seventy, Pinko, Elisabetta Franchi, Clementoni, Furlanis, Esemplare, Pal Zileri.

Reporting: Lead Strategist

- Led brands through competitor assessment.
- Created business decks for clients and new businesses
- Helped brands craft their essence: values, mission and vision.
  Helped brands define digital personas to comprise their digital space.
- Key bridge for cross-functional exchanges between design and business.
- Supported creative teams with briefs, visual territories and strategic scenarios.
- Inspired teams with consistent industry insights on market landscapes and new-age media.
- Developed brand bridges for Instagram content, guiding content teams through TOV and copy.
- Supported and conducted conducive customer journey workshops for new business possibilities.
- Conducted conducive research and analysis to develop and support brands' product and communication strategies.

# Freelance Brand & Communication Consultant, Mumbai, India (01.2016-08.2018)

Clients: NBA India, Lakmé Fashion Week (LFW), Renault India, Caprese, Lakmé, TRESemmé, Fashion designers, multi-designer luxury stores and production houses.

- Co-directed, styled and produced digital fashion campaigns and films for collection launches.
- Strategised disruptive branded content for LFW to stir change in fashion content consumption.
- Led content production team and first-of-its-kind real-time editing and broadcast for LFW content.
- Introduced NBA fashion to the Indian consumer, implementing a cultural cross-over strategy through a digital lookbook.

## **Professional Competencies**

- Brand Strategy.
- Creative Strategy.
- Creative Direction.
- Team Management.Client Management.
- Communication Strategy.

- Product Strategy.
- Decision Making.
- Writing and Presentation.
- Design Thinking and Sprint.
- Social Media Content Strategy.
- Qualitative Research and Interviews.

contribute to the success of a project. I am pursuing my MSc in marketing to further resonate, through the academic literature, how qualitative consumer behaviour and responsible marketing influence strategy and business decisions.

As a strategist, I aim to foster value-and-data-driven thinking through cross-functional, integrated, and inclusive strategy to address business challenges. My goal is to accelerate business growth by bridging the gap between businesses and consumers through ethical and sustainable practices, creating a symbiotic relationship between them.

# **Additional Work Experience**

#### Educator & Course Designer (Contract), Italy and India (05.2022-present)

Reporting: Director of Education

- Develop course material for Taught and Online courses with Design, Fashion and Business Schools: <u>Domus Academy</u> (Milan), The <u>Indian Institute of Art and Design</u> (IIAD) in association with Kingston School of Art, <u>Kingston University</u>, UK and <u>Istituto Marangoni</u>, Mumbai.
- Take Masterclass, workshops and online classes in Business Design and Business of Fashion subjects.

#### Educator, India (06.2014-08.2018)

Reporting: Head of Dept. for Fashion and Design

 Designed course material and taught and mentored fashion and communication students at Design and Fashion Schools in Delhi and Mumbai: <u>Pearl Academy</u> (Delhi & Mumbai), <u>ISDI with</u> <u>Parsons School of Design</u> (Mumbai) and <u>FAD Academy</u> (Mumbai).

# Senior Designer & Manager, New Delhi, India (08.2011-05.2014)

Reporting: Design Head

 During this period, I worked with an eclectic Fashion Design House and an E-commerce Brand, managing end-to-end design and production cycles, PR strategies and brand communication.

## **Education**

- MSc in Marketing (09.2023-09.2024)
- University of Bath, Bath, U.K.
- Workshop-based Master's (Level I) in Visual Brand Design (10.2018-07.2019)
   Domus Academy, Milan, Italy
- BA (Hons.) in Fashion Design (06.2007-05.2011)

Pearl Academy of Fashion, New Delhi, India, affiliated with Nottingham Trent University, U.K.

# **Software Skills**

- SPSS (Basic)
- Markstrat (Basic)Canva (Intermediate)
- Keynote (Intermediate)
- MS Office (Intermediate)
- Adobe Photoshop & InDesign (Basic)

# Languages

- Hindi (Bilingual)
- Italian (A1 level)English (Bilingual)
- English (Bilingual)
   Bengali (Bilingual)
- Derigali (Dililigual)

## Look forward to connecting!

With 8+ years of work experience in Brand Consulting, including 3+ years of Brand & Creative Strategy, I have managed multiple cross-disciplinary projects and overlapping deadlines in a fast-paced environment and start-ups. I am excited to share my professional journey and some exciting projects in an interview. I would love to get an opportunity to connect with you and chat further.

References are available on request.